[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many calories does 1 piece of mild chicken breast, offered in Popeyes, have?", "correct_answer": "350 calories", "incorrect_answers": ["250 calories", "280 calories", "300 calories"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the most recent volcano formed in the Western Hemisphere ?", "correct_answer": "Paricutin", "incorrect_answers": ["Mayon", "Yerupaja", "Guallatiri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a tort?", "correct_answer": "A law", "incorrect_answers": ["A kind of pie", "A type of computer", "A type of car"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carbon dioxide is a very common pollutant. Approximately how much carbon dioxide is produced by the average American each year?", "correct_answer": "22 tons", "incorrect_answers": ["5 tons", "93  tons", "1 ton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The giant sub atomic particle collider, capable of reproducing the big bang conditions, is located in which research facility?", "correct_answer": "CERN", "incorrect_answers": ["NASA", "None of these", "KAOS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many calories does 1 serving (8 fl. oz.) of skim milk contain?", "correct_answer": "80", "incorrect_answers": ["50", "70", "100"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements about conic sections is correct?", "correct_answer": "Every circle is an ellipse.", "incorrect_answers": ["Every parabola is an ellipse.", "Every cone is a parabola.", "Every ellipse is a ray."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fastest bird of prey?", "correct_answer": "Peregrine Falcon", "incorrect_answers": ["Harris Hawk", "Bald Eagle", "Osprey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can icebergs have blue streaks?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the crow has any interruption in her note like hiccup, or a croak with a kind of swallowing, it signifies this event.", "correct_answer": "Wind and rain", "incorrect_answers": ["Wind and tornado", "Fog and thunder", "Rain and haze"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. state has the huckleberry for its state fruit?", "correct_answer": "Idaho", "incorrect_answers": ["Kentucky", "Mississippi", "Iowa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Gary Oldman portray in the 2007 movie Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix, one of the highest-grossing movies in history?", "correct_answer": "Sirius Black", "incorrect_answers": ["Albus Dumbledore", "Lord Voldemort", "Ron Weasley"]}]